Nicholas Harrison

500 E Fremont St, Apt A203 Monroe, Washington 98272 (575) 499-4884 harrison.nick.15@gmail.com

Summary

Motivated and tech-savvy individual with years of electronics, information technology, and sales experience. Able to communicate effectively within a team and very keen to develop more professional skills, including building on graphic design experience. A creative problem solver who is solution focused and dedicated to the success of the team.

Education

University of Washington Coding Bootcamp

Seattle, WA

Pursuing the knowledge and knowhow of a Full Stack M.E.R.N. Web Developer to pursue a career in web development. Completed in September of 2020.

New Mexico State University - Carlsbad

Carlsbad, New Mexico

Pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Electrical and Computer Engineering.

Carlsbad High School

Carlsbad, New Mexico High School Diploma May 2015

Employment History

Domino's Pizza

Delivery Expert Seattle, Washington January 2020 - Present

Provide excellent and speedy delivery service for Domino's customers in my local area. Provided helping hand to manager and staff where needed.

Toyota of Lake City

Internet Sales Representative Seattle, Washington August 2018 – November 2019

Excellent customer service and in depth product knowledge. Use of IT based sales programming to track customers and provide consistent follow up.

Verizon Authorized Retailer – Cellular Sales

Sales Representative Carlsbad, New Mexico August 2017 – May 2018

Sales and customer service with in-depth product and service knowledge. Achieved top 50 sales person in the entire US consistently and provided service and support for the entire team.

United States Army

Motor Vehicle Operator Fort Leonard Wood, Missouri December 2014 – May 2016

Worked as an Employee for the United States Army. Transported people and/or units.

Nicks Computer Services And Tech Repair

Owner

May 2014 – August 2018

Tech repair: fixing phones, laptops, and desktops as well as software and malware installation, with the occasional light programming of small programs.

Professional Skills

Java Programming: Intermediate to Advanced C Programming: Intermediate to Advanced

JavaScript: Advanced ReactJS: Advanced HTML5: Advanced CSS: Advanced

Building Electronics: Advanced Python Programming: Competent

Soldering: Advanced

Following Directions: Advanced

References

Tae Lee

Previous Manager Toyota of Lake City (206) 310-4396 tlee@toyotaoflakecity.com

Alexander Hansen

Teacher at Coding Bootcamp Class Instructor (832) 605-1534 alex@alex-hansen.com

Kristy Bourgeois

Previous Coworker and Friend Verizon Authorized Retailer – Cellular Sales (575) 689-7954 kristy.bourgeois@cellularsales.com